let ques = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answer:  "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is making web Standard?",
        answer: "The World Wide Web Consortium" ,
        options: [
            "Google",
            "Microsoft",
            "Mozilla",
            "The World Wide Web Consortium"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "How many HTML file can we have on our project",
        answer:  "As many has required",
        options: [
            "Two",
            "Not more than one",
            "Not more than three",
            "As many has required"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?",
        answer:  "<br>",
        options: [
            "<br>",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the correct html extension",
        answer:  ".html",
        options: [
            ".js",
            ".css",
            ".html",
            ".asset"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is used to add tooltip",
        answer:  "Title",
        options: [
            "Paragraph tag",
            "Section tag",
            "Header",
            "Title"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is used to set width and font-size",
        answer:  "Px and %",
        options: [
            "Px and %",
            "*",
            "+",
            "-"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "_______ is used for image tag",
        answer:  "<img src>",
        options: [
            "<p></p>",
            "<section></section>",
            "<img src>",
            "<a>"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the correct html self closing tag",
        answer:  "Input",
        options: [
            "Paragraph",
            "section",
            "header",
            "Input"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answer:  "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup Language9",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "What is <a> used for",
        answer:  "It is used for linking html pages",
        options: [
            "To insert image on the website",
            "It can also be used to display input tag",
            "It is can only be used on header tag",
            "Are used to write a paragraph of text"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "What are HTML Attributes?",
        answer:  "Attributes are the properties that can be added to an HTML tag",
        options: [
            "Hyper",
            "Are marquee used for scrolling text on a web page",
            "Are used to write a paragraph of text",
            "This are tag used to define large quoted sections"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "What is the difference between HTML and CSS?",
        answer:  "HTML is used to create the structure and content of a web page, while CSS is used to define the appearance and layout of the page",
        options: [
            "They are both used to add javascript",
            "They both used for same purpose",
            "This is the functionality part of web",
            "HTML is used to create the structure and content of a web page, while CSS is used to define the appearance and layout of the page"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "How do you separate a section of texts in HTML?",
        answer:  "Using <br>",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup4 Language",
            "Using attributes",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Using <br>"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Define the list types in HTML?",
        answer:  "ol, ul",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup5 Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "ol, ul",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "How do you align list elements in an HTML file?",
        answer:  "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup6 Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Differentiate between an Ordered list and an Unordered list?",
        answer:  "An unordered list uses <ul> </ul> and ordered <ol> </ol>tags",
        options: [
            "An unordered list uses <ul> </ul> tags",
            "An unordered list uses <ul> </ul> and ordered <ol> </ol>tags",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "How do you create a hyperlink in HTML?",
        answer:  "We use the anchor tag <a> to create a hyperlink in HTML ",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup8 Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "What is semantic HTML?",
        answer:  " It is the use of HTML markup to reinforce the semantics or meaning of the conten",
        options: [
            "It is the use of HTML markup to reinforce the semantics or meaning of the conten",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "This is arrangement of tags on the webpage",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "What would happen if there is no text between the HTML tags?",
        answer:  "nothing will appear on the screen",
        options: [
            "nothing will appear on the screen",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answer:  "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool2 Markup Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "How do you create nested web pages in HTML?",
        answer:  "Nested web pages basically mean a webpage within a webpage",
        options: [
            "Nested web pages basically mean a webpage within a webpage",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "What are the different types of headings in HTML?",
        answer:  "Size",
        options: [
            "shape",
            "fix",
            "color",
            "background-color"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "What is the alt attribute in HTML?",
        answer:  "alternative",
        options: [
            "section",
            "alternative",
            "paragrahy",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "How do you add colour to the text in HTML?",
        answer:  "<style = color: red;",
        options: [
            "font-sixe",
            "style = color: red;",
            "position:relative",
            "align-item:center"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 26,
        question: "What is HTML used for",
        answer:  "Create the structure of a webpage",
        options: [
            "Create the structure of a webpage",
            "For styling webpage",
            "Make food",
            "Is for adding functionality to webpage"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 27,
        question: "How many HTML file can we have on our project",
        answer:  "As many has required",
        options: [
            "Two",
            "Not more than one",
            "Not more than three",
            "As many has required"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 28,
        question: "How do you separate a section of texts in HTML?",
        answer:  "Using <br>",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup4 Language",
            "Using attributes",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Using <br>"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 29,
        question: "Define the list types in HTML?",
        answer:  "ol, ul",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup5 Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "ol, ul",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 30,
        question: "How do you align list elements in an HTML file?",
        answer:  "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup6 Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 31,
        question: "Differentiate between an Ordered list and an Unordered list?",
        answer:  "An unordered list uses <ul> </ul> and ordered <ol> </ol>tags",
        options: [
            "An unordered list uses <ul> </ul> tags",
            "An unordered list uses <ul> </ul> and ordered <ol> </ol>tags",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 32,
        question: "How do you create a hyperlink in HTML?",
        answer:  "We use the anchor tag <a> to create a hyperlink in HTML ",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool Markup8 Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 33,
        question: "What is semantic HTML?",
        answer:  " It is the use of HTML markup to reinforce the semantics or meaning of the conten",
        options: [
            "It is the use of HTML markup to reinforce the semantics or meaning of the conten",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "This is arrangement of tags on the webpage",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 34,
        question: "What would happen if there is no text between the HTML tags?",
        answer:  "nothing will appear on the screen",
        options: [
            "nothing will appear on the screen",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 35,
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answer:  "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tool2 Markup Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 36,
        question: "How do you create nested web pages in HTML?",
        answer:  "Nested web pages basically mean a webpage within a webpage",
        options: [
            "Nested web pages basically mean a webpage within a webpage",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 37,
        question: "What are the different types of headings in HTML?",
        answer:  "Size",
        options: [
            "shape",
            "fix",
            "color",
            "background-color"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 38,
        question: "What is the alt attribute in HTML?",
        answer:  "alternative",
        options: [
            "section",
            "alternative",
            "paragrahy",
            "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 39,
        question: "How do you add colour to the text in HTML?",
        answer:  "<style = color: red;",
        options: [
            "font-sixe",
            "style = color: red;",
            "position:relative",
            "align-item:center"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 40,
        question: "What is HTML used for",
        answer:  "Create the structure of a webpage",
        options: [
            "Create the structure of a webpage",
            "For styling webpage",
            "Make food",
            "Is for adding functionality to webpage"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 41,
        question: "How many HTML file can we have on our project",
        answer:  "As many has required",
        options: [
            "Two",
            "Not more than one",
            "Not more than three",
            "As many has required"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 42,
        question: "Can HTML document has style within",
        answer:  "Yes, inline style can be done on html",
        options: [
            "Two",
            "Yes, inline style can be done on html",
            "No",
            "Not sure"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 43,
        question: "Which is the smallest header tag",
        answer:  "<h1>",
        options: [
            "<h2>",
            "<h3>",
            "<p>",
            "<h6>"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 44,
        question: "<p>Can be used to hold paragrahy on website",
        answer:  "Yes",
        options: [
            "No",
            "Not sure",
            "Sometimes",
            "Yes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 45,
        question: "All project most have html file",
        answer:  "Yes",
        options: [
            "No",
            "Not sure",
            "Yes",
            "As many has required"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 46,
        question: "What is used to set width and font-size",
        answer:  "Px and %",
        options: [
            "Px and %",
            "*",
            "+",
            "-"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 47,
        question: "There is no different between id and class",
        answer:  "As many has required",
        options: [
            "Two",
            "Not more than one",
            "Not more than three",
            "As many has required"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 48,
        question: "____________ is an example of attribute is HTML",
        answer:  "Class",
        options: [
            "Class",
            "<p>",
            "<main>",
            "<footer>"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 49,
        question: "How many HTML file can we have on our project",
        answer:  "As many has required",
        options: [
            "Two",
            "Not more than one",
            "Not more than three",
            "As many has required"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 50,
        question: "What is making web Standard?",
        answer: "The World Wide Web Consortium" ,
        options: [
            "Google",
            "Microsoft",
            "Mozilla",
            "The World Wide Web Consortium"
        ]
    },
    ];